Guide to the Allen Ginsberg film and video archive, 1983 - 1996
Department of Special Collections
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part VI. (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - "Brooklyn College Brain". (Folder 90)
    Time in: 15:04:55 Time out: 15:05:54 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Brooklyn College Brain..." Out: "... bird room."
  - "Drive All the Blames Into One", Take 1. (Folder 90)
    Time in: 15:06:37 Time out: 15:07:17 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Drive All Blames..." Out: "... I got hard--"
  - "Drive All the Blames Into One", Take 2. (Folder 90)
    Time in: 15:07:27 Time out: 15:07:35 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Drive All Blames..." Out: "... I didn't st--"
  - "Drive All the Blames Into One" Take 3. (Folder 90)
    Time in: 15:07:37 Time out: 15:08:19 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Drive All Blames..." Out: "... had a hard on."
  - "Howl". (Folder 90)
    Time in: 15:10:52 Time out: 15:12:06 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Howl..." Out: "... in underwear..."
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part VII. (Box 10, Folder 91)
  Time in: 16:00:00 Time out: 16:29:00 Total Time: 29m 09s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part VIII. (Box 10, Folder 92)
  Time in: 17:00:00 Time out: 17:29:00 Total Time: 29m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part IX. (Box 10, Folder 93)
  Time in: 18:00:00 Time out: 18:31:00 Total Time: 31m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part X. (Box 10, Folder 94)
  Time in: 18:31:00 Time out: 18:59:00 Total Time: 28m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part XI. (Box 10, Folder 95)
  Time in: 20:00:00 Time out: 20:30:00 Total Time: 30m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Ginsberg's last interview for The Life and Times of Allen Ginsberg, Boulder, CO, July 17, 1992. With Allen's published book of photographs.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part XII. (Box 10, Folder 96)
  Time in: 21:00:00 Time out: 21:13:00 Total Time: 13m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, July 17, 1992. Book of photographs only, close-ups of Allen's photos as he describes them.
- Ferlinghetti Interview, Part I. (Box 10, Folder 97)
  Time in: 1:01:11 Time out: 1:30:00 Total Time: 30m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  City Lights Book Store, upstairs office, San Francisco, CA, Spring 1992.
- Ferlinghetti Interview, Part II. (Box 10, Folder 98)
  Time in: 2:00:00 Time out: 2:31:00 Total Time: 31m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Beat Landmarks, San Francisco, Part I. (Box 10, Folder 99)
  Time in: 4:00:00 Time out: 4:09:00 Total Time: 9m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Various Landmarks in San Francisco, including City Lights Books, North Beach and others.
- Beat Landmarks, San Francisco, Part II. (Box 10, Folder 100)
  Time in: 3:00:00 Time out: 3:31:00 Total Time: 31m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Phillip Whelan Interview, Part I. (Box 11, Folder 101)
  Time in: 9:00:00 Time out: 9:31:00 Total Time: 31m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Phillip Whelan's house, San Francisco, CA, Spring 1992.
- Phillip Whelan Interview, Part II. (Box 11, Folder 102)
  Time in: 10:00:00 Time out: 10:28:00 Total Time: 28m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Michael McClure Interview, Part I. (Box 11, Folder 103)
  Time in: 5:00:00 Time out: 5:31:00 Total Time: 31m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Michael McClure's house, interior, Berkeley, CA, Spring 1992.
- Michael McClure Interview, Part II. (Box 11, Folder 104)
  Time in: 6:00:00 Time out: 6:24:00 Total Time: 24m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Michael McClure Interview, Part III. (Box 11, Folder 105)
  Time in: 7:00:00 Time out: 7:29:00 Total Time: 29m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Michael McClure Interview, Part IV. (Box 11, Folder 106)
  Time in: 8:00:00 Time out: 8:04:00 Total Time: 4m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg and Eugene Brooks at Walt Whitman Celebration, Part I. (Box 11, Folder 107)
  Time in: 3:14:00 Time out: 4:41:00 Total Time: 30m 0s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Huntington, NY, 1991. More sound than picture; at times sound continues under black image.
  - Introductions. (Folder 107)
    Time in: 3:13:00 Time out: 3:54:00 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Filmed at Walt Whitman's birthplace, Huntington, NY.
  - Audience sings "Happy Birthday". (Folder 107)
    Time in: 4.31.00 Time out: 4:33:00 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Eugene reads poetry. (Folder 107)
    Time in: 4:35:00 Time out: 4:41:00 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg and Eugene Brooks at Walt Whitman Celebration, Part II. (Box 11, Folder 108)
  Time in: 5:16:00 Time out: 5:51:00 Total Time: 30m 0s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Eugene Brooks reads poem and cries. (Box 11, Folder 109)
  Time in: 5:16:00 Time out: 5:24:00 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen Ginsberg reads Whitman and own poems. (Box 11, Folder 109)
    Time in: 5:24:00 Time out: 5:51:00 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen Ginsberg and Eugene Brooks at Walt Whitman Celebration, Part III. (Folder 109)
    Time in: 6:56:00 Time out: 8:13:00 Total Time: 30m 0s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen reads poetry. (Folder 109)
    Time in: 6:56:50 Time out: 6:59:04 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen and Eugene accept award. (Folder 109)
    Time in: 7:56:42 Time out: 7:58:42 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg and Eugene Brooks at Walt Whitman Celebration, Part IV. (Box 11, Folder 110)
  Time in: 8:25:00 Time out: 8:39:00 Total Time: 30m 0s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  More sound than picture; at times sound continues under black image. Filmed at Walt Whitman's birthplace, Huntington, NY.
- Anne Waldman Interview, Part I. (Box 12, Folder 111)
  Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:28:00 Total Time: 28m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Spring 1992, Boulder, CO. Anne Waldman describes her visit to Prague with Ginsberg in the mid-1990's, as Ginsberg returned to reclaim his "King of May" crown.
  - Visit to Prague story, Take 1. (Folder 111)
    Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:04:00 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Anne Waldman with distracting scarf and noisy earring.
  - Visit to Prague story, Take 2. (Folder 111)
    Time in: 1:04:00 Time out: 1:10:59 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Anne Waldman without scarf and earring.
  - Visit to Prague story, Take 3. (Folder 111)
    Time in: 1:10:59 Time out: 1:28:00 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Anne Waldman, best exposure. Same information as on Takes 1 and 2, but technically better.
- Anne Waldman Interview, Spring 1992, Part II. (Box 12, Folder 112)
  Time in: 2:00:00 Time out: 2:28:00 Total Time: 28m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Spring 1992, Boulder, CO. Interview continues interspersed with Anne reading her poetry.
- Allen Ginsberg Teaches Class, Part I. (Box 12, Folder 113)
  Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:29:00 Total Time: 29m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, July 23, 1992. Ginsberg prepares to teach, teaches and reads poetry to his students.
  - Before Class. (Folder 113)
    Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:14:00 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg prepares to teach.
  - Class Proper. (Folder 113)
    Time in: 1:14:00 Time out: 1:21:08 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg teaches his poetry students about Whitman.
  - Two Poems. (Folder 113)
    Time in: 1:24:10 Time out: 1:29:16 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Andy Clausen, poet, recites two of his poems to the poetry class.
- Allen Ginsberg Teaches Class, Part II. (Box 12, Folder 114)
  Time in: 2:00:00 Time out: 2:29:00 Total Time: 29m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, July 23, 1992. Ginsberg recites two of his poems to the students in his poetry class.
- Allen Ginsberg Teaches Class, Part III. (Box 12, Folder 115)
  Time in: 3:00:00 Time out: 3:10:00 Total Time: 10m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg: "Howl", Part I. (Box 12, Folder 116)
  Time in: 6:32:00 Time out: 6:47:00 Total Time: 15m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Auditorium of the Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, July 25, 1992. Stage left.
- Allen Ginsberg: "Howl", Part II. (Box 12, Folder 117)
  Time in: 8:26:00 Time out: 8:53:00 Total Time: 27m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg: "Howl", Part III. (Box 12, Folder 118)
  Time in: 8:54:00 Time out: 9:03:00 Total Time: 9m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg: "Howl", Part IV. (Box 12, Folder 119)
  Auditorium of the Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, July 25, 1992. Stage right. Matches action of Tape 116.
- Allen Ginsberg: "Howl", Part V. (Box 12, Folder 120)
  Time in: 8:17:00 Time out: 8:37:00 Total Time: 20m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Auditorium of the Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, July 25, 1992. Stage right. Matches action of Tape 117.
- Allen Ginsberg: "Howl", Part VI. (Box 13, Folder 121)
  Time in: 8:32:00 Time out: 9:04:00 Total Time: 32m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Auditorium of the Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, July 25, 1992. Stage right. Matches action of Tape 118.
- Andy Warhol Interview; Julian Beck and Judith Malina Interview. (Box 13, Folder 122)
  Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:16:42 Total Time: 16m 42s Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Subjects interviewed in New York City in 1985.
  - Andy Warhol Interview. (Folder 122)
    Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:05:27 Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Interview location: Warhol's Studio in Manhattan.
  - Interview: Living Theater founders, Julian Beck and Judith Malina. (Folder 122)
    Time in: 1:05:40 Time out: 1:16:42 Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Interview location: The Holly Solomon Gallery in Manhattan.
- Early Jazz Footage; Selects from Rudy Burckhardt. (Box 13, Folder 123)
  Time in: 1:01:21 Time out: 1:43:37 Total Time: 25m 59s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Selected scenes from film and television, including Charlie Parker and Dizzy Gillespie and neon light in New York City in the 1940's.
  - Early Jazz Footage: Charlie Parker and Dizzy Gillespie. (Folder 123)
    Time in: 01.01.21 Time out: 01.13.34 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Scenes from an old television program showing Parker and Gillespie playing music and accepting an award, including stills and close-ups.
  - Selects from Rudy Burckhardt: Square Times. (Folder 123)
    Time in: 01.13.49 Time out: 01.20.26 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    This short color film by Rudy Burckhardt depicts the Times Square of the early forties.
  - Selects from Rudy Burckhardt: Climate of New York. (Folder 123)
    Time in: 01.37.47 Time out: 01.43.37 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    This short black and white film by Rudy Burckhardt depicts the Times Square of the early sixties.
- USA Poetry: Allen Ginsberg. (Box 13, Folder 124)
  Time in: 21.01:00 Time out: 21:29:00 Total Time: 28m 0s Source: 3/4" Enhanced Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Allen Ginsberg and Neal Cassady in the basement of City Lights Books, San Francisco, 1965.
  - Allen Ginsberg reading poetry to the camera. (Folder 124)
    Time in: 21:01:00 Time out: 21:02:05 Source: 3/4" Enhanced Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads the newly written ending of the poem: "King of May" ("Kral Majales").
  - Allen Ginsberg showing poster. (Folder 124)
    Time in: 21:02:12 Time out: 21:04:24 Source: 3/4" Enhanced Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Neal Cassady watches as Ginsberg shows his Buddhist poster used for picketing against the Vietnam War.
  - Allen Ginsberg and Neal Cassady. (Folder 124)
    Time in: 21:04:25 Time out: 21:11:36 Source: 3/4" Enhanced Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Cassady discuss the military and the world situation.
  - Allen Ginsberg. (Folder 124)
    Time in: 21:11:37 Time out: 21:13:00 Source: 3/4" Enhanced Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg plays small chimes and chanting.
  - Allen Ginsberg and Neal Cassady. (Folder 124)
    Time in: 21:13:01 Time out: 21:17:41 Source: 3/4" Enhanced Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    They discuss William Carlos Williams, Kerouac, Corso, Ezra Pound, and Russian poets.
  - Allen Ginsberg's San Francisco apartment. (Folder 124)
    Time in: 21:17:42 Time out: 21:27:39 Source: 3/4" Enhanced Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg, Cassady and brothers Julius and Peter Orlovsky get ready to leave apartment on VW bus.
  - Allen Ginsberg at Robert LaVigne's studio. (Folder 124)
    Time in: 21:27:40 Time out: 21:29:00 Source: 3/4" Enhanced Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen describes LaVigne's painting Foster's Cafeteria.
- USA Poetry: Ginsberg and Ferlinghetti. (Box 13, Folder 125)
  Time in: 1:00:10 Time out: 1:28:59 Total Time: 28m 49s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Narrated television program from 1966 about Allen Ginsberg and Lawrence Ferlinghetti.
  - Allen Ginsberg. (Folder 125)
    Time in: 1:00:57 Time out: 1:05:49 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads a portion of the poem "Who Be Kind To."
  - Rober LaVigne's painting. (Folder 125)
    Time in: 1:06:06 Time out: 1:08:45 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg describes the history surrounding the painting Foster's Cafeteria.
  - Allen Ginsberg reading a portion of the poem "King of May" in San Francisco. (Folder 125)
    Time in: 1:09:02 Time out: 1:10:56 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    While we hear Ginsberg's reading, we see Ginsberg's apartment. People present include Neal Cassady, Peter and Julius Orlovsky and Ginsberg.
  - San Francisco. (Folder 125)
    Time in: 1:10:57 Time out: 1:11:39 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    VW bus ride to Robert LaVigne's studio.
  - LaVigne painting a portrait. (Folder 125)
    Time in: 1:11:40 Time out: 1:14:39 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Orlovsky play music while LaVigne paints.
  - Allen Ginsberg in Robert LaVigne's studio, San Francisco (Folder 125)
    Time in: 1:14:40 Time out: 1:19:08 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads a portion of the poem "New York to San Francisco".
- Jack Kerouac Funeral; Joan Baez Interview. (Box 13, Folder 126)
  Time in: 3.21:09 Time out: 4:10:01 Total Time: 21m 3s Source: Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Gregory Corso shot 16mm film at Kerouac's funeral in Lowell, Massachusetts in 1969. Joan Baez was interviewed in Denver, CO, at the Rainbow Music Hall August 4, 1984.
  - Jack Kerouac Funeral. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 3:21:09 Time out: 3:37:01 Total Time: 8m 10s Source: 16mm Color Film Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Gregory Corso shot 16mm film at Kerouac's funeral in Lowell, Massachusetts in 1969.
  - Jack Kerouac Funeral: moving footage. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 3:21:09 Time out: 3:24:33 Source: 16mm Color Film Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg, as a pallbearer, walks down the front steps of a church.
  - Jack Kerouac Funeral: still frames. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 3:24:34 Time out: 3:28:59 Source: 16mm Color Film Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    4 stills of Kerouac's casket as it is carried from the church.
  - Jack Kerouac Funeral: moving footage. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 3:29:00 Time out: 3:29:54 Source: 16mm Color Film Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The funeral procession follows the hearse and at the burial site.
  - Jack Kerouac Funeral: still frames. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 3:30:43 Time out: 3:36:02 Source: 16mm Color Film Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    2 stills of the procession and graveyard.
  - Jack Kerouac Funeral: moving footage. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 3:36:17 Time out: 3:37:01 Source: 16mm Color Film Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Home movies of Ginsberg, Corso and others.
  - Joan Baez Interview. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 3:58:14 Time out: 4:10:54 Total Time: 12m 53s Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    This interview takes place in Denver, CO, at the Rainbow Music Hall.
  - Joan Baez Interview, false start. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 3:58:14 Time out: 3:59:17 Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The interview begins, then is halted a minute into it.
  - Joan Baez Interview. (Folder 126)
    Time in: 4:00:22 Time out: 4:10:54 Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The complete interview.
- Additional Kerouac Funeral Stills. (Box 13, Folder 127)
  Time in: 6:26:41 Time out: 07.13.48 Total Time: 15m 25s Source: 16mm Color Film Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  18 still frames from Gregory Corso's 16mm footage of Kerouac's Funeral in Lowell, Massachusetts, 1969. Jumps in Time Code.
- Norman Mailer Interview; Allen Ginsberg CIA Protest. (Folder 128)
  Time in: 2:00:03 Time out: 2:29:22 Total Time: 29m 13s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master D2 Master
  Norman Mailer opens up about the details of his friendship with Ginsberg. Ginsberg protests the CIA at the University of Colorado, Boulder.
  - Norman Mailer Interview, Boulder, CO, 1985. (Folder 128)
    Time in: 2.00.03 Time out: 2.17.05 Total Time: 17m 2s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master D2 Master
    New transfer 6/23/99. Best quality image of this interview. Includes Mailer discussing his and Ginsberg's involvement at the 1968 Democratic Convention.
  - University of Colorado: CIA protest with Ginsberg arrest, Boulder, CO, April 11, 1985. (Folder 128)
    Time in: 2.17.11 Time out: 2.29.22 Total Time: 12m 11s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master D2 Master
    Footage goes in and out of synch. This was a non-violent protest ending in many arrests.
- Timothy Leary Interview. (Box 13, Folder 129)
  Time in: 1.00.00 Time out: 1.21.20 Total Time: 21m 20s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Ginsberg Narration of First Photo Exhibit. (Box 13, Folder 130)
  Time in: 3:00:00 Time out: 3:16:42 Total Time: 16m 42s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Exhibit at the Holly Solomon Gallery, New York City, 1985.
- Hannah Litsky Interview. (Box 14, Folder 131)
  Time in: 2.00.01 Time out: 2.23.40 Total Time: 22m 41s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  West Orange, New Jersey, 1985. Picture ends at 2:10:54. The sound continues as Litsky (also known as "Aunt Honey") describes home movies of Ginsberg.
  - The following video tapes contain many still photographs of Ginsberg, his family and friends. (Folder 132141)
    Time in: Time out: Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Photos have been animated by a variety of camera moves.
- Ginsberg, Family and Friends: Photos 1-9. (Box 14, Folder 132)
  Time in: 1:00:44 Time out: 1:20:43 Total Time: 19m 59s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Many early family photos including Allen's parents.
- Ginsberg, Family and Friends: Photos 10-25. (Box 14, Folder 133)
  Time in: 2:00:34 Time out: 2:20:45 Total Time: 20m 12s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  There are many early family photos including Ginsberg as a baby, his parents and Eugene. Also, photos of his mother's institution.
- Ginsberg, Family and Friends: Photos 26-39. (Box 14, Folder 134)
  Time in: 3:00:32 Time out: 3:18:54 Total Time: 18m 22s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A few photos of Ginsberg as a young man and photos of young Corso, Carr, Kerouac and Burroughs.
- Ginsberg, Family and Friends: Photos 40-54. (Box 14, Folder 135)